although inkscape is meant to be a
尽管Inkscape旨在成为一种
vector design app that doesn't mean it
矢量设计应用程序并不意味着它
can't be used to edit photos as well
也不能用来编辑照片
in fact i'd even go as far as saying
事实上，我甚至可以说
that inkscape can handle certain photo
Inkscape可以处理某些照片
editing tasks better than some
编辑任务比某些任务更好
pixel-based editors
基于像素的编辑器
one example of such would be when
这种情况的一个例子是当
applying color overlays to your
将颜色覆盖应用于您的
photographs which we'll be demonstrating
我们将演示的照片
in today's tutorial
在今天的教程中
[Music]
[音乐]
before we get started with the lesson
在我们开始上课之前
i'd just like to take a moment to give a
我只想花点时间给你一个
special thank you to expressvpn for
特别感谢您对Express VPN的支持
sponsoring today's video
赞助今天的视频
expressvpn helps you secure your privacy
Express VPN帮助您保护您的隐私
when browsing the internet they do this
当他们浏览互联网时，他们会这样做
by routing your network activity through
通过以下方式路由您的网络活动
their secure and encrypted servers not
他们的安全和加密服务器不
only does this prevent your isp from
只有这样才能阻止您的互联网服务提供商
seeing your web browsing activity but it
看到你的网页浏览活动，但它
also makes it more difficult for
也让它更难做到
advertisers websites and government
广告商、网站和政府
agencies to track you by allowing you to
代理机构通过允许您跟踪您
mask your ip address
掩码您的IP地址
expressvpn only invests in premium
Express VPN只投资于保费
servers which makes them consistently
使他们始终如一的服务器
faster than other vpns they offer 24 7
他们提供的VPN全天候比其他VPN更快
customer support if you ever need it and
如果您需要客户支持，
setting it up couldn't be easier in just
设置它不能再简单了
a few clicks i was able to connect and
点击几下我就能连接到
continue on with all of my design
继续我的所有设计
research with the peace of mind of
安心研究
knowing that my privacy is secure
知道我的隐私是安全的
expressvpn is your all-in-one vpn
Express VPN是您的一体式VPN
provider click the link in the
提供程序单击
description below to sign up today and
今天要注册的说明如下所示
get three months for free
免费获得三个月
so to get us started here i'm first
所以为了让我们从这里开始，我首先
going to show you how to do this
我将告诉你如何做到这一点
manually using a single color with blend
手动使用具有混合的单一颜色
modes and then i'll show you how to do
模式，然后我会告诉你怎么做
this using the duo chrome filter in
使用中的双铬滤镜
inkscape
墨迹
so the first thing i want to do here is
所以我想要做的第一件事是
import my image onto the canvas now
立即将我的图像导入画布
there's various different ways to do
有各种不同的方法来做
this but my preferred way of importing
这是我更喜欢的进口方式
images is to just click and drag the
图像是只需单击并拖动
image file onto the canvas let me show
把图像文件放到画布上让我展示
you what i mean here if i bring in my
你知道我的意思是如果我把我的
folder with my image all i have to do is
文件夹中有我的图像，我要做的就是
just click and drag this onto the canvas
只需点击并将其拖到画布上
like that and then i will get this
像这样，然后我就会得到这个
little prompt right here that asks me if
这里有一个小提示符，问我是否
i want to embed or link it i'm going to
我想嵌入或链接它，我要
choose to embed the image and click ok
选择嵌入图像，然后单击确定
and there you go as you can see the
这就是你可以看到的
image has been embedded
图像已嵌入
so let me zoom out now i'm going to hold
所以现在让我把镜头拉远，我要按住
ctrl and roll down my mouse wheel to
按住Ctrl键并向下滚动鼠标滚轮以
zoom out a little bit so i have a better
缩小一点，这样我就能有一个更好的
look at this and to move my page around
看看这个，然后移动我的页面
i'm just pressing down the mouse wheel
我只是按下鼠标滚轮
and moving the mouse
并移动鼠标
now what i want to do is resize the
现在我想要做的是调整
document to be the same size as this
文档的大小应与此相同
image right here so with this image
图像就在这里，所以这张图像
selected press ctrl shift and r on the
选定的按住Ctrl Shift和r键
keyboard and it will change the document
键盘，它将更改文档
to be resized around this image okay so
在这张图片周围调整大小好的，所以
now what i want to do is i want to
现在我想做的是我想要
create a rectangle and make it the same
创建一个矩形并使其相同
size as this image so let me right click
大小与此图像相同，因此让我右键单击
this image and go to copy
此图像并转到复制
let me grab the rectangle tool over here
让我拿一下这边的矩形工具
and i'm going to click and drag on my
我要点击并拖动我的
canvas to create a rectangle it doesn't
画布来创建它不能创建的矩形
need to be the same size as the image it
需要与图像大小相同
just needs to be any size we're going to
只要是我们要达到的任何大小
address that right now we just go to
地址现在我们只需转到
edit go to paste size and select paste
编辑转到粘贴大小，然后选择粘贴
size and it's going to take the image
大小和它将采取的图像
size that i have copied to my clipboard
我已经复制到剪贴板上的大小
and apply it to that rectangle now i'm
然后把它应用到那个矩形上，现在我
going to grab the selection tool and i'm
我要拿起选择工具，然后我
going to change the color of this
我要改变这个的颜色
rectangle to whatever color i'd like my
长方形到我想要的任何颜色
overlay to be so for this example i will
叠加成这样对于本例，我将
use a blue shade so i'll come down here
用蓝色的遮阳板，这样我就会下来
to my palette and i will choose a shade
到我的调色板，我会选择一种色调
of blue like that
像这样的蓝色
and now i want to center this up over
现在我想把这件事集中在
the image so let me hold shift and click
该图像让我按住Shift键并单击
on the image so i have both the
在图像上，所以我既有
rectangle and the image selected and i
矩形和选定的图像，然后我
will open up the align the distribute
将打开对齐分布
menu which is located over here you can
位于这里的菜单，您可以
also access that by pressing ctrl shift
也可以通过按Ctrl Shift键访问该选项
and a on your keyboard
和键盘上的
within the align the distribute menu i
在对齐分发菜单中
want to make sure that i have the
想要确保我有
relative two set to last selected and
设置为上次选定的相对两个AND
then once that's enabled we can center
一旦启用，我们就可以居中
it vertically and horizontally like that
它是这样垂直和水平的
and as you as you can see the rectangle
正如你所看到的，这个矩形
should be directly over the image now
现在应该就在图像的正上方
so let me click off of the graphic to
因此，让我从图表中单击以
deselect everything i'm going to select
取消选择我要选择的所有内容
just this rectangle right here and now
就在此时此地的这个长方形
i'm going to open up the fill and stroke
我要打开填充物和划线
menu which is located up here or you can
菜单位于此处，或者您可以
access it by pressing ctrl shift and f
按Ctrl Shift键和f键即可访问
on the keyboard
在键盘上
[Music]
[音乐]
once we are in the fill and stroke menu
一旦我们进入填充和描边菜单
if you look down here to the bottom
如果你从这里往下看到底部
right of the menu you will see this drop
在菜单的右侧，您将看到这个下拉列表
down menu for blend modes by default the
默认情况下，混合模式的下拉菜单
blend mode is set to normal meaning this
混合模式设置为正常，这意味着
rectangle looks like a normal rectangle
矩形看起来像一个普通的矩形
with a solid fill
使用实心填充
we can change the way that this object
我们可以改变这个物体的方式
interacts with objects positioned
与放置的对象交互
beneath it though by changing this blend
在它的下面，通过改变这种混合
mode let me show you what i mean here
模式让我向您展示我在这里的意思
i'm going to change this to multiply
我要把这个改成乘法
and as you can see it changes the
正如您所看到的，它改变了
appearance of the image or the way that
图像的外观或方式
the rectangle interacts with the image
该矩形与图像交互
beneath it and if i use my arrow keys i
在它下面，如果我使用我的箭头键
can cycle through all of the different
可以在所有不同的
blend modes we have here until i find
我们这里的混合模式，直到我找到
the color overlay that i prefer
我更喜欢的颜色覆盖
now this one right here seems to work
现在这里的这个似乎起作用了
pretty well the effect i'm looking for
很好，我想要的效果是
is just a simple color overlay and what
只是一个简单的颜色覆盖和什么
this one does the color blend mode it
这个是做混色模式的吗？
just takes the color and applies it over
只需获取颜色并将其应用于
the image nicely like that without
没有那张照片很像那幅画
making too many other changes i should
做了太多我应该做的改变
mention though that every single image
尽管如此，每一张图片
is different so if you're working with
是不同的，所以如果您正在使用
the image a different image than this
这个图像与这个图像不同
you may want to cycle through these
您可能希望循环浏览这些内容
blend modes to see which one works best
混合模式以查看哪种模式效果最好
now as you can see here if i take this
现在如你所见，如果我拿着这个
object and move it off of the image over
对象，并将其从图像上移出
there you can see it looks the same as
在那里你可以看到它看起来和
it did before the only difference is the
以前是这样的，唯一的区别是
way it interacts with the objects
它与物体相互作用的方式
beneath it like that and if you don't
就像这样，如果你不这样做
like how this works and you want to go
就像这是怎么运作的，你想去
back to having a regular solid fill
回到常规的实体填充
rectangle at any point you could just
任何点上的矩形，您可以只需
select it and set the blend mode back to
选择它并将混合模式设置回
normal like that and as you can see it's
就像你看到的，这很正常
now a regular rectangle again
现在又是一个规则的矩形
so now let's have a look at an arguably
所以现在让我们来看看有争议的
easier and maybe even better way to do
更简单，甚至更好的方法来做
this using the duochrome filter and
这使用双色滤光片和
inkscape
墨迹
so what i'm going to do is i'm going to
所以我要做的是我要
select my image right here and i'm going
就在这里选择我的形象，我就会
to come up here to where it says filters
到这里来，上面写着过滤器
i'm looking for color and then i will
我在寻找颜色，然后我会
choose duochrome
选择双色
and once you've done that you're going
一旦你这样做了，你就会去
to get this little menu right here
才能在这里拿到这个小菜单
the first thing i want to do with this
我想做的第一件事就是
menu is where it says live preview i
菜单上显示实时预览I
want to enable that checkbox right there
我想在那里启用该复选框
and as you can see when i enabled that
正如您所看到的，当我启用该功能时
it applied two different colors to my
它将两种不同的颜色应用到我的
image it applied the color blue to the
它将蓝色应用于
darker shades and it applied the color
较深的色调，并应用了颜色
green to the lighter shades and the
从绿色到浅色调和
reason why is because color one up here
原因是因为上面的颜色一
in this tab is set to blue and color two
在此选项卡中设置为蓝色和颜色二
up here in this tab is set to green now
此选项卡中的此处现在设置为绿色
if you want to change your colors you
如果你想改变你的颜色
could do so very easily up here say for
可以很容易地做到这一点，比方说
example i want to change the darker
例如，我想更改较暗的颜色
shades from blue to something else like
从蓝色到其他颜色，比如
pink i can do that as well if i want to
粉色的，如果我想的话我也可以这么做
i can change this like that
我可以把这个改成那样
and there we go now we have pink in the
现在我们开始了，我们有粉色的
darker shades i may even want to make
我甚至可能想要做更深的色调
this a little darker so you can see it
这个稍微暗一点，这样你就能看得见了
better but i'm sure you get the idea
好多了，但我相信你会明白
that's one way that you can do that
这是你可以做到这一点的方法之一
and if i come over here to color two i
如果我来这里给两个我涂上颜色
could change that the lighter shades to
可以将较浅的色调改为
something like yellow to change up how
像黄色这样的东西来改变如何
that works
工作的
okay and once you're finished you can go
好的，完成后你就可以走了
ahead and click apply
前进并点击申请
and then close out of the menu that is
然后关闭菜单
how you can go about applying a simple
如何应用简单的
color overlay or even a duotone effect
色彩叠加甚至双色调效果
to a photograph using inkscape if you
如果您使用水墨景观拍摄照片
have any questions let me know and as
有任何问题请告诉我并作为
always thanks for watching
始终感谢观看
[Music]
[音乐]